zno.com 2017-05-19

# Zno - Privacy policy

Zno Privacy Policy

By using Zno, you agree to the following Privacy Policy.

Collecting Personal Information

When you register on our websites, mobile sites, and mobile applications we will collect and save your email, first name and last name. 

When you place an order on our websites, mobile sites, and mobile applications we will collect and save your shipping addresses. 

When you pay for an order on our websites, mobile sites, and mobile applications with a credit card we will collect your credit card #, expiry date and CSC for that single transaction but we will not save your credit card information unless you are purchasing a membership plan with a recurring monthly fee. 

When you have successfully finished placing an order on our websites and mobile sites you can volunteer the name of your photography business if applicable. If you volunteer the name of your business we will save it. 

Using Personal Information

We will use your email, first name, last name, shipping address, and credit card to fulfill your requests for products and services, administrative purposes, to improve our services, to customize the advertising and content you see, to contact you, and for internal business purposes. 

Collecting Technical Information

When you access our websites, mobile sites or mobile applications we will collect non-personally-identifiable information including browser type, operating system, domain names, and IP Address. In addition we use "cookies" to keep you automatically logged in from any device you have previously accessed us from. 

Using Technical Information

We will use your non-personally-identifiable technical information to improve the usability of our websites, mobile sites, and mobile applications. 

Collecting Content Information

Any image uploaded to our server will be automatically collected and saved until deleted by the user who uploaded the image. Any project created will be automatically collected and saved until deleted by the user who created the project. If a project has been ordered it can no longer be deleted. 

Using Content Information

On our websites and mobile sites at the end of checkout on the confirmation page a user will be given the voluntary option to authorize Zno to share the images contained in that order on Zno's social media and promotional material. Authorization allows Zno to share one or all images from that order at any time in the future and to alter the size of images to fit social media or other media. Zno is not responsible for users who accidentally authorize images to be shared. Zno is not responsible for water marking images before sharing. Zno is not responsible for incorrectly attributing images. Zno is not responsible for other social media users or website users who download or share images that are featured in Zno's social media or websites without owners permission. Zno will attempt to delete images from social media and websites under Zno's control after posting if subsequently requested by owner, but if images cannot be found or deleted Zno is not responsible. 

If the owner of a project shares their project using the "share url" or "embed code" we are not responsible for where the project is distributed. 

Zno reserves the right to delete any images that you upload if Zno determines that your images are inappropriate for any reason, scenarios may include copyrighted or pornographic images. We are not responsible for providing copies of these deleted images. 

Children Under Age 13

You must be at least 13 years or older to register and use Zno. If you are under 13, you must use an account created by a parent of guardian, and you must have the explicit permission of a parent of guardian to use Zno. 

Security

We use a secure server, which encrypts our sign-in page, sign-up page and all payment data. For extra security we do not store your credit card information in our database unless you are purchasing a membership plan with a recurring monthly fee. 

Updating Privacy Policy

This privacy policy may be changed by Zno with or without notice. Please review this page regularly for changes. Continued use of this web site following any change constitutes your acceptance of the change.
